Guide to the Second Stage Theater Records, 1973 - [ongoing]
Second Stage Theater Records, 1973 - [ongoing]
  - Fall 1992
    - Lloyd's Prayer (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Frankie and Johny in the Chair de Lune (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Faculty Dance (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Psyche Sycophant (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - The Stickwife (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Visible Rhythms (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Lying: A Tale for Friends (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Pay the Chinaman/ As the Crow Flies (was Yankee Dawg You Die/A Life in the Theater) AACT (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - In Your Face (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Seduced (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Show Applications (Box 10, Folder 12A)
    - Show App Responses (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Administrative (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Correspondences and Notes (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Spring 1993
    - Staff/Season Lists (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Cancer Research Society (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - The Typists and the Tiger (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Hawaiian Wedding Song (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Actors' Nightmare (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Battle of the Bands/ an evening with Gag Reflex (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Oddfellows (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Yankee Dawg You Die AACT (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Ritual (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - The economic rite of passage Center Research Society (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Thesis Dance (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - French Plays The French Play (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - WesRevue (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Visible Rhythms (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Show Applications (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Staff Applications (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Administrative (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Correspondence and Notes (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - 1992-1993
    - Budget and Finances (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Fall 1993
    - Staff and Season (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Club 92 (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - The Lover (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - In Trousers (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Faculty Dance (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - No Exit (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Marvin's Room Senior Project (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - Terpsichore (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - Puppet Hack/Blaker (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - Women and Technology Llambelis (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - Show Applications (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - Administrative (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - Correspondence and Notes (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Spring 1994
    - Staff/Seasons (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Gag Reflex (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Love Songs for Reagan Babies (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Women and Wallace (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - The Portable Life (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Lounge Allure (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Asa Ga Kimashita Morning has Broken AACT (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Top Girls (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Who's Afraid of Virginia Woolf? (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Firebugs (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Thesmophoriazusae (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Spring Dance (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Terpsichore/ Visible Rhythms (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - WesRevue (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Show Applications (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Show App Response (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Administrative (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence and Notes (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - 1993-1994
    - Budget and Finances (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Fall 1994
    - Staff/Season (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - A…my name is Alice (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Talk to me like the rain and let me listen AND Three more sleepless nights (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Beyond Therapy (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Faculty Dance (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Waiting for Godot (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Terpsichore (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Rosencrantz and Guildenstern are Dead (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - AACT (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Six Degrees of Separation (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - For Colored Girls Who Considered Suicide when the Rainbow is Enuf (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - The Colored Museum (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Visible Rhythms (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Show Applications (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Show App Responses (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Administrative (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Spring 1995
    - Annual Reports (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - 1/27/1995 Friends of Old Time Music (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - 2/4/1995 WesRevue (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - 2/9-11/1995 Steel Magnolias (Box 11, Folder 38A)
    - 2/16-18/1995 Two One Acts (Box 11, Folder 39)
    - 2/16-18/1995 Thus Spake the Mallard (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - 2/23-25/1995 Oh Dad, Poor Dad (Box 11, Folder 41)
    - 3/2-4/1995 Summer and Smoke (Box 11, Folder 42)
    - 3/2-4/1995 Barking at the Word (Box 11, Folder 43)
    - 3/30-4/1/1995 Blaker Puppet Show (Box 11, Folder 44)
    - 4/7-8/1995 Thesis Dance (Box 11, Folder 45)
    - 4/13-15/1995 Terpsichore (Box 11, Folder 46)
    - 4/20-22/1995 E-Love (Box 11, Folder 47)
    - 4/20-22/1995 AACT (Box 11, Folder 48)
    - 4/27-29/95 Kafka's Dick (Box 11, Folder 49)
    - 5/4-6/95 Lesser Islands (Box 11, Folder 50)
    - Applications (Box 11, Folder 51)
    - Application Responses (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - 1994-1995
    - Budget (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - Fall 1995
    - Documents (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - 10/12-14/1995 Into the Woods (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - 10/26-28/1995 Omar's Show (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - 11/3-4/1995 Faculty Dance (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - 11/9-11/1995 AACT (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - 11/16-18/1995 Harold and Maude (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - 11/30-12/1/1995 Jeffrey (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - 12/7-9/1995 Spiked Heels (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - 12/14-16/1995 Terpsichore (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Applications (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - 1995-1996
    - Budget/ Finances (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - 1995-1998
    - Minutes (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Spring 1996
    - Documents (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - 2/8-10/1996 Day Room (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - 2/15-17/1996 Pterodactyls (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - 3/28-30/1996 Terpsichore (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - 4/5-6/1996 Thesis Dance (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - 4/5-6/1996 WesRevue (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - 4/18-20/1996 Two One Acts (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - 4/26-27/1996 Spring Dance (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - 5/2-4/1996 Bodega (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Show Applications (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Fall 1996
    - Documents (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - 9/26-28/1996 A life in the Theatre (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - 10/3-5/1996 Prom Queens Unchained (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - 10/17-19/1996 Oleanna (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - 10/10-12/1996 Rhapsody (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - 11/1-2/1996 Faculty Dance (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - 11/7-9/1996 Three One Acts (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - 11/14-16/1996 Journey Beyond the East (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - 11/21-23/1996 Luv (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - 12/5-7/1996 Harris-Cronin Senior Project Woyzeck (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - 12/12-14/1996 Death and the Maiden (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Spring 1997
    - Applications (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - Documents (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - Staff / Season (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - 2/20-22/1997 The night Thoreau spent in Jail (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - 2/27-3/1/1997 Grand Magic (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - 1/23-25/1997 Slow Children at Play (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - 4/4-5/1997 Thesis Dance (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - 2/6-8/1997 Tongues (Box 12, Folder 41)
    - 1/30-2/1/1997 WesRevue (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - 3/27-29/1997 Terpsichore (Box 12, Folder 43)
    - 4/10-12/1997 Marriage of the Cobra (Box 12, Folder 44)
    - 4/17-19/1997 Criminal Hearts (Box 12, Folder 45)
    - Applications (Box 12, Folder 46)
    - Application Replies (Box 12, Folder 47)
    - Administration (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - 1996-1997
    - Budget (Box 12, Folder 48A)
  - Fall 1997
    - Documents (Box 12, Folder 49)
    - 9/25-27/1997 America Hurray (Box 12, Folder 50)
    - 11/7-9/1997 Two One Acts (Box 12, Folder 51)
    - Fall of the City (Box 12, Folder 52)
    - Eastern Standard (Box 12, Folder 53)
    - The Problem (Box 12, Folder 54)
    - Terpsichore (Box 12, Folder 55)
    - Two One Acts- Counting the Ways & Hamlet Machine (Box 12, Folder 56)
    - Fool for Love (Box 12, Folder 57)
    - Someone Who'll Watch Over Me (Box 12, Folder 58)
  - Spring 1998
    - Administration (Box 12, Folder 59)
  - Fall 1998
    - Staff Applications (Box 12, Folder 60)
    - Documents (Box 12, Folder 61)
    - Clippings (Box 12, Folder 62)
    - Scrapbook materials (1998-99) Clippings/ Programs (Box 12, Folder 63)
  - 1998-1999
    - Notebook (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Spring 1999
    - Documents (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - 7 Minutes in Heaven (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - AACT -Laughing out loud (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Picasso at the Lapin Agile (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Rose and Renter (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Comedy Festival (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Three Tall Women (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Cryptogram (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - WesReview '99 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Yes, and... (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - A Short Evening of Short Comedy Shorts (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Terpsichore (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - 25th Anniversary Festival (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Applications (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Administration (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Fall 1999
    - Documents (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - How I Learned to Drive (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Holy Ghostly & She Talks to Beethoven (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Lysistrata (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Compleat Works of Wllm Shkspr (Abridged) (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Moving Passages (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Terpsichore (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Our Town (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Masterclass (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Wasp & the man with the flower in his mouth (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - No Exit (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Devour (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Oh Hell (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Applications (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Spring 2000
    - Staff/Season (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Equus (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - In the Heights (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - Zoo Story (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - Terpsichore (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - Around the Corner (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - Turn of the Screw (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - Wonderland (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - The Trestle at Pope Lick Creek (Box 13, Folder 40)
    - The Fantastiks (Box 13, Folder 41)
    - Romancers (Box 13, Folder 42)
    - Food Chain (Box 13, Folder 43)
    - Why we have a body (Box 13, Folder 44)
    - No play (Box 13, Folder 45)
    - The Wire (Box 13, Folder 46)
    - Applications (Box 13, Folder 47)
    - Adminstration (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - Fall 2000
    - Documents (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Waiting for Lefty (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Icarus's Mother (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - God (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Breathing (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Benefit One-Act Festival (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - The Dumb Show (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Stupid Kids (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Hell's Mouth (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - The Threepenny Opera (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Dr. Faustus (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Dumb Waiter (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Terpsichore (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Fall Faculty Dance (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - The Shadow Box (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Applications (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Administration (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Spring 2001
    - Documents (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Betrayal (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - T Bone N Weasel (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Skylight (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Measure for Measure (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Momo (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Sex, Death, Dance (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Once on this Island (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - I'm Fine…Really. (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Red, White, and Rocky (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Wrong for Each Other (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Rebirth in Third Person (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - The Bad Seed (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Kyogen (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Dark Ages (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Stop/Kiss (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - The Lorax (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - Precision Dance (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - Private Eyes (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - Runaways (Box 14, Folder 37)
    - The Vagina Monologues (Box 14, Folder 38)
    - Terpsichore (Box 14, Folder 39)
    - Applications (Box 14, Folder 40)
    - Staff Interest Spring 2001 (Box 14, Folder 41)
    - Administration (Box 14, Folder 42)
    - Correspondence (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - 2000-2001
    - Budget & Finances (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - Fall 2001
    - The Real Inspector Hound/ The Most Massive Woman Wins (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Escapology (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Infernal Cake Walk (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - J.B. (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - the WOMAN Plays (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Basketcase (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Art (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Terpsichore (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - The Valentine Story (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - A Lie of the Mind (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Homecoming (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - True West (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Show Applications (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Applications (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Spring 2002
    - Documents (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Wife Swap (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Titanic (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Terpsichore (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Every Good Play Ends with a Crucifiction [sick] (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Riff Raff (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Falsettos (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Star-Spangled Girl (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Precision (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Boy Gets Girl (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Vagina Monologues (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - The Air (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Burn this Set (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Show Contracts (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Applications (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Interest Forms/ Staff Applications (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Administration (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - 2001-2002
    - Budget & Finances (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Fall 2002
    - Documents (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - Bash (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - Cyrano (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - The Attic (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - Defying Gravity (Box 15, Folder 37)
    - Sponsorship Application (Box 15, Folder 38)
    - Show Applications (Box 15, Folder 39)
    - Administration (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Spring 2003
    - Documents (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Glengarry Glen Ross (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Never Swim Alone (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Foetus Follies (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Romeo and Juliet (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - The American Dream (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Gored (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Echoes of Eden (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Performed Pieces Confessionaire (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Applications (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - 2002-2003
    - Budget & Finances (Box 16, Folder 10a)
  - Fall 2003
    - Documents (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Buffy the Musical (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Gross Indecency (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Want's Unwisht Work (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - This is a Play (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Terpsichore (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Show Applications (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - A Mouse that Roared (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Show Applications (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Staff Applications (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Show Applications Flier (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Administrative (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Spring 2004 (Box 22)
    - Account Numbers for Second Stage Plays Fall 2004/Spring 2005
    - Show Apps Spring '04
    - Sponsorship Contracts
    - Woyzeck
    - The Importance of Being Ernest
    - Pounding Nails
    - Precision
    - Picasso at the Lapin Agile
    - A View from the Bridge
    - Edmond
    - The Fantasticks
    - Nightclub Cabaret (An Evening at the Hotbox)
    - A Three Night Affair
    - Meditations (These Things of Ours): A Love Story
    - Quills
    - The Butterfly's Evil Spell
    - Keep It Movin'
  - Fall 2004 (Box 22)
    - The Game We Used to Play
    - WASP
    - No Sex Please, We're British
    - The House of Blue Leave
    - Senior Thesis Film
    - Life x 3
    - Wesleyan Playwrights' Collective Showcase
    - Pirates vs. Ninjas
  - Spring 2005 (Box 22)
    - Staff Applications
    - Application for Second Stage Sponsorship: Dance Thesis
    - Poster for The Altruists
    - Application for Second Stage Sponsorship:The Altruists
    - Aunt Dan and Lemon
    - The Waiting Place
    - Wesley Gultch Melodrama
    - Reverse Transcription
    - Sunspots
  - Fall 2005 (Box 22)
    - Application for Second Stage Sponsoprship: Terpsichore
    - Chiang Kai Chek
    - Line
    - The Exonerated
    - The Complete Works of William Shakespeare (Abridged)
    - Sexual Perversity in Chicago
    - Metamorphosis
    - Vienna: Lusthaus
    - The Faculty Room
    - The Frogs
    - Staff Applications
  - Spring 2006 (Box 22)
    - Show Apps Spring '06
    - Urinetown
    - Rebecca Josue Senior Thesis
    - Precision
    - The Lion in Winter
    - March of the Falsettos
    - Being Ordinary
    - Hamlet
    - Ubu Roi
    - Melodrama
    - The Sail Against the Wind
    - The Shape of Things
    - Spalding Gray Is Missing
    - Dark Holler
    - We Can't Reach You, Hartford (Scotland Project)
    - Frogman
  - Fall 2006 (Box 23)
    - Staff Applications
    - Show Apps Fall '06
    - Allocation Request Form from the SBC
    - Heart Play(s)
    - Life and Death in the Charity Ward
    - The Same House
    - Manuscript
    - Western Civilization: The Complete Musical (Abridged)
    - Refugee
    - Electrica
    - Interesting Times
  - Spring 2007 (Box 23)
    - Show Applications
    - Staff Applications
    - Staff Applications
    - 365 Days/ 365 Plays
    - The Vagina Monologues
    - Pan O'Rama
    - The Family of Mann
    - After Ashley
    - The Beast with Two Backs
    - Melodrama
    - The Coffin Is Too Big for the Hole
    - Orpheus
    - 24 Hour Play Festival
    - Nina Cohodes Resignation
  - Fall 2007 (Box 23)
    - Show Applications
    - Falling
    - Miss[(ed) It]
    - Tape
    - Smolapalooza
    - Haul Down Finer Fates
    - Rosencrantz and Guildenstern Are Dead
    - Kitchen Poems
    - The Showcase
    - Jaws: The Musical
    - A Comedy of Errors
    - A Day in the Death of Joe Egg
    - Oh Dad, Poor Dad, Mamma's Hung You in the Closet and I'm Feeling So Sad
    - Marisol
    - Staff Applications
  - Spring 2008 (Box 24)
    - Random Goodies
    - Show Apps
    - Vagina Monologues
    - Matt and Ben
    - Precision
    - Look, What I Don't Understand
    - My Kingdom for a Whore
    - Pampliset
    - Ashpet
    - The Good Red Road
    - The Real Thing
    - We Are Monsters Without a Name
    - Icarus
    - Everything Was Just a Thing
    - The Sunset Limited
    - Musiophobia
    - Staff Apps
  - Fall 2008 (Box 24)
    - Show Apps
    - Random Season Goodies
    - Senory Overload
    - Don't Look Up (Seven Minutes in Heaven)
    - Patterns of Inheritance
    - Wait Until Dark
    - The Pillowman
    - Home Free
    - Somewhere in the Middle
    - The Kotov Syndrome
    - The Peot and the Rent
    - Songs for a New World
    - The Rocky Horror Picture Show
    - Production Reports Fall '08
  - Spring 2009 (Box 25)
    - Show Apps
    - Life in the Brain
    - Outreach Weekend
    - The Shy Courtier
    - Black Friday
    - How to Be a Man in West Belfast
    - She Unnames Them
    - Dinosaurs Do Chekhov
    - Precision
    - On Edge
    - Bump, Splice, Claim
    - Rage
    - What Is Blue Where You Are (Forearm)
    - Ridgefield Middle School Talent Night
    - Sunday in the Park With George
    - The Ways We Hold
    - Heart Playz
    - No Face Theater (The Secret Science of Forgetting)
    - Valentine's Day
  - Unarranged materials
    - Project Book (Box 17)
      1 binder.
    - Project Book Additional Materials
    - Calendar for Theater Dept, '06-'07
    - Blue folder of sketches
    - Party Info (defunct as of 1986)
    - Old posters which may be useful
    - Unlabeled folder
    - Milwaky Vac
    - Staff 2000
    - Budget
    - Staff Interest Notes
    - Renovations
    - Returned Second Stage Applications
    - Second Stage The Books (Box 18)
    - Inventories
    - Misc.
    - Shop
    - Flyers
    - Lights
    - Meeting sheets
    - Show Applications
    - Keeping 10 Fingers, 99/00
    - Borrowing Contracts, 99/00
    - Development--Old Ideas
    - Late Night/High Noon
    - Addendums
    - Original Second Stage Info Sheets, Fall 1993
    - How to Run the Directors Meeting (for 2nd Stage Staff)
    - Lock-up in the '92
    - Rules of 92
    - Alt Space Guideslines (2 pages)
    - Chapel ground plan
    - Pine St. Rules
    - Campus Center
    - Armando's Magic MPR Map
    - Res Life Lounge
    - TA/TD Responsibilities
    - Alternate Spaces
    - Sound and Booth
    - Forms
    - Sound Co-op
    - Unidentified Script
    - Posters and Programs, undated
    - Clippings
    - Stage designs
    - Costumes and Makeup
    - Small Idea Proposals
    - Fire Marshall
    - Miscellaneous
    - Loose materials
      Gathered into 2 folders.
  - Oversized
    - Posters (Box 19-20)